Tired of your quiet routine?
厌倦了平静的日常生活？
How about leaving your computer games behind and taking up an extreme sport?
何不放下电脑游戏，开始一项极限运动呢？
You can ride a bicycle, right?
你会骑自行车，对吧？
In that case you're halfway to becoming a mountain biker.
那样的话，你已经离成为一名山地自行车手不远了。
All you have to do is take your bike off the road and try some rough terrain.
你所要做的就是将自行车骑离公路，尝试一些崎岖地形。
Mountain biking was developed in California in the 1970s and became an Olympic sport in 1996.
山地自行车运动于20世纪70年代在加利福尼亚发展起来，并于1996年成为奥运会项目。
In the London 2012 games athletes had to navigate a 4.7-kilometre track in less than two hours.
在2012年伦敦奥运会上，运动员们必须在不到两小时内完成4.7公里的赛道。
Not challenging enough?
还不够有挑战性？
Skydivers jump from aircraft at an altitude of 1,000 to 4,000 metres.
跳伞者从1000到4000米高空的飞机上跳下。
You have to be fit but there's no age limit with this sport.
你必须身体健康，但这项运动没有年龄限制。
Dilys Price from Cardiff went on her first jump aged 54.
来自卡迪夫的迪莉丝·普莱斯（Dilys Price）在54岁时尝试了她的第一次跳伞。
The minute she came down she wanted to go up again.
她一落地就想再跳一次。
"I was hooked", said Dilys.
“我上瘾了，”迪莉丝说。
Some adrenaline junkies are even bolder – they've invented base jumping, in which people leap from tall structures, such as buildings or bridges, with a parachute.
一些肾上腺素瘾君子甚至更大胆——他们发明了低空跳伞（base jumping），即人们使用降落伞从建筑物或桥梁等高耸结构上跳下。
Many of their stunts aren't legal, especially in urban areas.
他们的许多特技并不合法，尤其是在城市地区。
Dan Witchalls has jumped off The Shard - London's 310 metre-high skyscraper - four times.
丹·威查尔斯（Dan Witchalls）曾四次从伦敦310米高的摩天大楼“碎片大厦”跳下。
He says: "Base jumping is scarier than jumping out of a plane.
他说：“低空跳伞比从飞机上跳伞更可怕。
In a plane there's no perception of height, but when you are standing on the edge of the building you can see people and cars - it makes it very real."
在飞机上，你感觉不到高度，但当你站在建筑物的边缘时，你可以看到人和车——这使得这项运动非常真实。”
It seems there's no lack of imagination when it comes to risking life to look cool and get the heart pounding.
在冒着生命危险让自己看起来很酷并让心跳加速方面，似乎从不缺乏想象力。
Surfing, scuba diving, rock climbing…
冲浪、潜水、攀岩……
How about turning one of your chores into a daredevil pursuit?
何不将你的一项家务变成一项大胆的消遣？
'Extreme ironing' isn't for wimps!
“极限熨烫”可不是懦夫的游戏！
Pressing your shirt on top of a mountain could be dangerous, depending on the mountain.
在山顶上熨烫衬衫可能会很危险，这取决于山的高度。
Extreme ironing is said to have been created in the 1990s in the English town of Leicester by a man who saw a pile of wrinkled clothes and felt bored.
据说，极限熨烫是20世纪90年代由英格兰莱斯特镇的一名男子发明的，他当时看到一堆皱巴巴的衣服感到非常无聊。
That was Phil Shaw who also won the only Extreme Ironing Championships ever held, in Germany in 2002.
这个人就是菲尔·肖（Phil Shaw），他还在2002年德国举办的迄今为止唯一一届极限熨烫锦标赛中获胜。
For him, the thrill of this sport comes from looking at the spectators' faces.
对他来说，这项运动的刺激来自于观察观众的表情。
Shaw says: "Sometimes they look confused, sometimes they laugh.
肖说：“有时他们看起来很困惑，有时他们会笑。
It's fun to see how people respond to it."
看到人们的反应很有趣。”